Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ phucnguyen0329 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Azure Gitlab DevOps

Languages

English (Limited Working)

Certifications

SCRUM MASTER ACCREDITED CERTIFICATION

Phuc Nguyen

Senior DevOps Engineer at Metanet

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

With over 9 years of experience as an Infrastructure Engineer/
DevOps professional, I also excel as a team leader. My expertise spans DevOps automation, containerization, and orchestration using CI/CD, Docker, and Kubernetes. I've led teams in crafting robust on-premise and cloud infrastructures, collaborating closely with architects for top-tier designs on MS Azure Cloud. Additionally, I oversee application administration, troubleshooting, system automation, scripting, and project execution. My track record includes setting up tailored Azure Cloud infrastructures and effectively managing CI/CD pipelines.

Experience

Metanet 메타넷 4 years 10 months

Senior DevOps Engineer
June 2020 - Present (4 years 10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

DevOps Engineer August 2020 - Present (4 years 8 months) Bitexco

Swiss Post Solutions

2 years 5 months

Application Administrator April 2018 - August 2020 (2 years 5 months) Vietnam

DevOps Engineer April 2018 - August 2020 (2 years 5 months) Vietnam

DXC Technology

Associate DevOps Engineer September 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 7 months)

Education

International University - VNU HCMC
Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Information Technology in
Networking · (2010 - 2015)